Great.
太好了。
Family game night ruins another Saturday.
家庭游戏之夜又毁了一个星期六。
Mae just invited me over for Mae-ke Your Own Pizza Night.
梅刚刚邀请我去参加梅-凯自制披萨之夜。
That's when they make pizzas at Mae's.
就是在梅家做披萨的时候。
And now I can't go.
现在我去不了了。
Well, we want to go to movie night at Conner's.
嗯，我们本来想去康纳家的电影之夜。
That's when we go watch movies...
就是我们去康纳家看电影的时候...
at Conner's.
在康纳家。
Okay.
好吧。
We all have things we'd rather do,
我们都有自己更想做的事情，
so tonight's the night.
所以今晚就是那个晚上。
We got to tell Mom and Dad
我们得告诉爸爸妈妈
we don't want to do game night anymore.
我们不想再参加家庭游戏夜了。
Yeah.
是啊。
We're allowed to have lives too.
我们也有自己的生活。
It's time to take a stand.
是时候站出来了。
No more family game night.
不再有家庭游戏夜。
- Who's ready for family game night?
谁准备好参加家庭游戏夜了？
- Best night of the week!
一周中最棒的夜晚！
- Woot! - Woot!
哇！哇！
Why aren't you wooting?
你为什么不欢呼？
Mom, Dad...
妈妈，爸爸...
Before we woot,
在我们欢呼之前，
we want to talk to you about game night.
我们想和你们谈谈游戏夜的事。
I'm getting the sense you're not super excited about game night.
我感觉你们对游戏夜不是特别兴奋。
Yeah, do you guys not want to do game night anymore?
是啊，你们是不是不想再玩游戏夜了？
[all] [gently] No!
[所有人] [温和地] 不！
- Great. I'll get the pencils. - I'll get the snacks.
- 太好了。我去拿铅笔。 - 我去拿零食。
Maybe tonight's not the night.
也许今晚不是那个夜晚。
Right. Plan B.
对。执行B计划。
We lose every game and get family lame night over with
我们每局都输，早点结束这无聊的家庭之夜
so we can go to Conner's and you can go to Mae's.
这样我们就可以去康纳家，你去梅家。
Great.
太好了。
So operation "We lose every game
所以行动计划是‘我们每局都输
"and get family lame night over with
‘早点结束这无聊的家庭之夜
so we can go to Conner's and you can go to Mae's"
这样我们就可以去康纳家，你去梅家’
is a go.
行动开始。
This is why we don't let you name operations.
这就是我们不让你命名行动的原因。
Okay, okay, okay.
好了，好了，好了。
Boom...
砰...
chaka-laka!
查卡-拉卡！
[both shouting]
[两人同时喊叫]
Guess you win.
看来是你赢了。
- Yeah! - Yeah! Whoo!
- 耶！ - 耶！哇！
Ready?
准备好了吗？
Right foot green.
右脚绿色。
Ahh!
啊！
I pulled a hammy!
我拉伤了腿筋！
Yeah!
耶！
Ricky got hurt!
里基受伤了！
You want us to call you a wahmbulance?
你想让我们给你叫辆救护车吗？
Wahhhh!
哇！
If we were in London, it would sound like this:
如果我们现在在伦敦，听起来会是这样：
Wah-wah, wah-wah,
哇-哇，哇-哇，
wah-wah.
哇-哇。
Seriously, are you okay?
说真的，你还好吗？
I'm fine.
我没事。
Great. You guys win again.
太好了。你们又赢了。
Yes!
耶！
Okay, another game night in the books.
好的，又是一个游戏之夜记录在册。
Done in record time.
以创纪录的时间完成了。
I guess we're on our own for the rest of the night.
我想今晚剩下的时间我们得靠自己了。
No, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不！
There's more.
还有更多。
Tonight's the perfect night
今晚是完美的夜晚
to unveil a little surprise we've been working on:
来揭晓我们一直在准备的一个小惊喜：
The Harper Family Trivia Game.
哈珀家族知识问答游戏。
Here's a teaser:
这里有个预告：
Which second cousin moved to Wisconsin
哪位表亲搬到威斯康辛州
solely for his love of cheese?
纯粹是因为他对奶酪的热爱？
Think about that
想想那个
while we get the game.
在我们准备游戏的时候。
I wish Mom and Dad had something else to do on Saturday nights
我希望妈妈和爸爸周六晚上能有别的事情做
besides ruin ours.
而不是毁了我们的。
Yeah.
是啊。
They need some friends so they can go out once in a while.
他们需要一些朋友，这样他们偶尔可以出去一下。
Dicky, that's it.
迪基，就是这样。
They just need friends.
他们只是需要朋友。
We need to get Mom and Dad a life so we can have one too.
我们需要给妈妈和爸爸找个生活，这样我们也能有自己的生活。
All in?
都准备好了吗？
I got it.
我明白了。
The cheese man is our cousin Jack.
卖奶酪的是我们表亲杰克。
He's from Monterrey.
他来自蒙特雷。
Ohhh.
哦。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
Okay.
好的。
We all want our Saturday nights free, right?
我们都希望周六晚上自由，对吧？
[all] Yeah.
是的。
So who looks like they'd be a good match for Mom and Dad?
那么，谁看起来像是适合妈妈和爸爸的人选呢？
Ooh. Look no further.
哦，不用再找了。
They're perfect.
他们太完美了。
Ooh. Look no further.
哦。别再找了。
It's perfect.
这很完美。
Let's look further.
我们再看看别的。
What about those two?
那两个怎么样？
They look perfect.
他们看起来很完美。
That's Mom and Dad.
那是爸爸妈妈。
What about those two?
那两个呢？
[Dream Weaver playing]
[《织梦者》播放中]
You mean those two testing the fans?
你是说那两个在测试风扇的吗？
Yeah!
是的！
All right.
好吧。
Operation "No More Game Night"
行动“不再有游戏之夜”
is a go.
开始了。
That's how you name an operation.
这就是你给行动命名的方式。
So, you guys fans of these fans?
所以，你们是这些风扇的粉丝？
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
I'll say.
我得说。
They're pretty fan-tastic!
他们真是太棒了！
So, can we help you find something?
那么，我们能帮你找点什么吗？
Such great service.
服务真棒。
Could you direct us to the fishing section?
请问钓鱼用品区怎么走？
This one's a big fisherman.
这位可是个钓鱼高手。
So's our dad!
我们爸爸也是！
Fishing section's this way.
钓鱼用品区这边请。
I'm sorry, could you repeat that?
抱歉，能再说一遍吗？
I have a little bit of a herring problem.
我有点小麻烦，关于鲱鱼的。
[all laugh]
（大家都笑了）
He's just kidding. He did that on porpoise.
他开玩笑的。他是故意的。
Ohh!
哦！
[sighs]
[叹气]
They're the ones.
就是他们。
Our work here is done.
我们这里的工作完成了。
I don't know, guys.
我不知道，伙计们。
They mispronounce a lot of words.
他们很多单词都发音不准。
Okay, there are the customers who need help.
好的，那些是需要帮助的顾客。
Okay, we're going, we're going!
好的，我们走了，我们走了！
So, deep sea's your game, huh?
所以，深海是你的强项，嗯？
Oh, I dabble.
哦，我稍微涉猎一下。
Tom Harper.
汤姆·哈珀。
This is my first mate, Anne.
这是我的大副，安妮。
Oh, we're the Milbanks.
哦，我们是米尔班克夫妇。
- I'm Phil. - I'm Bonnie.
- 我是菲尔。- 我是邦妮。
Come on, Phil, give it up.
得了吧，菲尔，别藏着了。
Best catch.
最棒的收获。
Ten-foot swordfish off the coast of Barbados.
在巴巴多斯海岸捕到的一条十英尺长的剑鱼。
- Wow! - Yeah.
- 哇！- 是啊。
Take me there.
带我去那儿。
It's working.
起作用了。
Here's something you don't see every day.
这可是难得一见的景象。
You've got a purse
你有一个手提包
and you've got a purse.
你也有一个手提包
[gasps]
[吸气声]
Looks like you two have got a purse-onal connection.
看来你们俩有了一种手提包的私人联系
Yours is beautiful.
你的很漂亮
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢
I got it in London.
我在伦敦买的
You love London.
你喜欢伦敦
You know what my favorite part is?
你知道我最喜欢什么吗？
The sirens.
警笛声
[both] Wah-wah, wah-wah, wah-wah!
And then boom!
Ten foot of swordfish sashimi is flipping at me feets.
- Wow. - Yeah.
I've always dreamt that one day I'd...
meet someone with a story like that.
And now you have.
And perhaps he has pictures.
Well, if it's fish pics you're into,
I may have one or two thousand.
Hey, bon-bon, come on over here.
嘿，小甜心，过来这边。
I'm showing the fish pics.
我在展示鱼的照片。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看看那个。
Huh?
嗯？
Um, Mr. and Mrs. Harper,
嗯，哈珀先生和哈珀太太，
hi.
嗨。
So, my favorite band is playing this weekend
所以，我最喜欢的乐队这个周末要演出
and the only way to get tickets is if you camp in line,
而且唯一能买到票的方法就是排队露营，
so I was wondering if I could borrow a tent.
所以我想知道我能不能借个帐篷。
Sure, whatever.
当然，随便什么。
- And a sleeping bag? - Sure, whatever.
- 还有睡袋吗？ - 当然，随便。
Can I leave now and have the weekend off?
我现在可以走了，周末休息吗？
Sure, whatever.
当然，随便。
Amazing!
太棒了！
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
[all sigh]
[大家都叹气]
So...
所以...
They're blowing it.
他们搞砸了。
Do something!
做点什么！
Watch me work.
看我操作。
Offer them a smoothie.
给他们提供一杯冰沙。
Hey, could we offer you a smoothie?
嘿，我们可以给你提供一杯冰沙吗？
We'd love a smoothie!
我们很想要一杯冰沙！
That was a great idea!
那真是个好主意！
It just popped in there!
它就那样突然冒出来了！
Well, that went more smoothie than we thought.
嗯，这比我们想象的要顺利得多。
Josie, we need a round of--
乔西，我们需要再来一轮——
Where's Josie?
乔西在哪儿？
Bye, Phil.
再见，菲尔。
Bye, Bonnie.
再见，Bonnie。
- I--yeesh! - Oh!
我...哎呀！- 哦！
So?
所以呢？
When are you crazy kids getting together again?
你们这些疯狂的孩子什么时候再聚啊？
We didn't talk about anything like that.
我们没聊过那种事。
Well, maybe you should call them
那你或许应该给他们打个电话，然后，你知道的，聊聊那种事。
and, you know, talk about things like that.
- 呃。- 啊，我不知道。
- Ehh. - Ah, I don't know.
哇哦。
Whoa.
停车场里的是他们吗
Is that them in the parking lot
正在和其他酷炫的大人说话？
talking to some other cool adults?
在停车场里和其他酷酷的大人聊天？
Make the call.
打个电话吧。
We don't want to seem desperate.
我们不想显得太急切。
[phone rings]
[电话铃响]
[gasps] They're calling us!
[倒吸一口气] 他们在给我们打电话！
[gasps] What do we do?
[倒吸一口气] 我们该怎么办？
[all] Answer it!
[大家] 接电话！
- What do I say? - I don't know!
- 我说什么好？ - 我也不知道！
Just be yourself.
就做你自己。
- I can do that. - Okay, okay.
- 我可以做到。 - 好的，好的。
Tomcat Harper here. Meow!
我是Tomcat Harper。喵！
I mean roar!
我是说，吼！
Why am I making animal noises?
我为什么要学动物叫？
Yes. Yes, it was great meeting you too.
是的，是的，见到你也很高兴。
Oh, really great!
哦，真的非常棒！
Yeah, that was Anne-cat Harper.
对，那是Anne-cat Harper。
Grr!
呜！
Yeah--yes, we would love to get together again.
是的——是的，我们很愿意再聚一次。
Oh, Saturday?
哦，星期六？
That's actually our family game night.
实际上那天是我们家的家庭游戏夜。
- It's fine. - Go ahead.
- 没关系。 - 说吧。
Don't worry about us.
别担心我们。
Do it!
去做吧！
Oh, why not?
哦，为什么不呢？
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
Saturday night it is.
那就周六晚上吧。
It's official.
就这么定了。
We're seeing the Milbanks Saturday night!
我们周六晚上要见Milbanks一家！
Oh, good-bye family game night!
哦，再见家庭游戏夜！
[all] Yes!
[所有人] 太好了！
And they're bringing their kids
而且他们还带了孩子
for double family game night!
来个双重家庭游戏夜！
[all] No!
不要！
Wait, you guys don't want to do double family game night?
等等，你们不想来个双重家庭游戏夜吗？
[all] [gently] No!
不想！
Great!
太好了！
[all groan]
（大家都叹气）
[sighs] I can't, Mae.
（叹气）我不能去，Mae。
I'm stuck here again for family game night.
我又得被困在这里参加家庭游戏夜。
What?
什么？
You're making ice cream sundaes
你在做冰淇淋圣代
with unlimited toppings?
而且配料无限吗？
Aw, nuts.
哎，糟糕。
And cherries?
还有樱桃吗？
Well, that's the topper.
嗯，那是最顶级的。
Have fun.
玩得开心。
We're never gonna leave this house.
我们永远都离不开这房子了。
Maybe Mom and Dad will do something embarrassing
也许爸爸妈妈会做出什么尴尬的事情
and scare them off.
把他们吓跑。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
[Tom] We'll get it!
This looks promising.
- What do you think? - You like our fedoras?
They are perfect...
for Operation "Mom and Dad do something embarrassing
and scare them off."
What did I tell you?
[gasps]
No way!
You have got to be kidding me.
You look fedorable!
你看起来太可爱了！
You look fedorabler!
你看起来更可爱！
Aw!
啊！
On the bright side,
从好的方面看，
it can't get any worse.
不能再糟糕了。
And now presenting the fedorablest:
现在介绍最可爱的：
Jill, Will, and Phil Jr.
吉尔，威尔和小菲尔。
- ♪ Hello ♪ - ♪ Hello ♪
♪ 你好 ♪
♪ Hello ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪ - ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ 哦，不 ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
Oi.
喂。
We brought this on ourselves.
我们这是自找的。
There's still hope.
还有希望。
Not for Nicky.
对尼基来说没有。
[all] ♪ Nicky, Nicky, Nicky, Nicky ♪
♪ 尼基，尼基，尼基，尼基 ♪
♪ Nicky, Nicky, Nicky, Nicky ♪
I told you we could turn any name into a song.
我告诉过你，我们可以把任何名字变成一首歌。
It's gonna be fine.
一切都会好的。
Once the games start,
一旦比赛开始，
Mom and Dad will get super competitive
爸爸妈妈会变得超级有竞争力
and scare the Milbanks away.
然后把Milbanks一家吓跑。
Why take that chance?
为什么要冒这个险？
Follow my lead.
跟着我做。
Listen, there's something you should know about our parents.
听着，关于我们的父母，有些事你应该知道。
Oh, dear.
哦，天哪。
Our mom and dad are super competitive.
我们的爸爸妈妈超级有竞争力。
Ohh, double dear.
哦，双重天哪。
Phil. Language.
菲尔，注意措辞。
[sighs] So take a good look at those friendly faces.
[叹气] 所以好好看看那些友好的面孔。
It's the last time you're gonna see them tonight.
今晚你最后一次见到他们了。
Well, thanks for telling us, kids.
嗯，谢谢你们告诉我们，孩子们。
Uh, Tom?
呃，汤姆？
Anne?
安妮？
Sorry to have to tell you this, but we're gonna have to leave...
很抱歉不得不告诉你们，但我们不得不离开...
you in the dust!
把你们甩在后面！
Milbanks!
米尔班克斯！
- Ha ha! - Yeah!
哈哈！ - 耶！
Let the double family game night commence!
双家庭游戏之夜开始！
[air horn blows]
[空气喇叭吹响]
[all] Game night! Game night! Game night! Game night!
[众人] 游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！
What have we done?
我们做了什么？
[all] Game night! Game night! Game night! Game night!
[众人] 游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！
Game night! Game night! Game night! Game night!
游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！游戏之夜！
[all whispering]
[众人低语]
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- 耶！ - 耶！
[Phil] Nice pull, Will!
[菲尔] 干得好，威尔！
[all] Will! Will! Will! Will!
[众人] 威尔！威尔！威尔！威尔！
Zip!
拉链！
Now put that baby to bed.
现在把那小家伙放床上。
Sleep tight, little one.
睡个好觉，小宝贝。
[all cheer]
大家欢呼
All right!
好极了！
Zip!
拉链！
You're up.
轮到你了。
Don't pay any attention to them.
别理他们。
What do I do?
我该做什么？
Well,
嗯，
if we have to join them,
如果我们必须加入他们，
we might as well beat these game night freaks.
我们不妨打败这些游戏夜的怪人。
Let's do this.
我们开始吧。
[all] One, two, three, Harpers!
[所有人] 一，二，三，哈珀斯！
Want some fries with that shake, boy?
要来点薯条配那奶昔吗，小子？
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
Okay, Dawn.
好的，Dawn。
Right hand blue.
右手蓝色。
Can't reach it, Dawn.
够不到，Dawn。
Give up.
放弃吧。
Never!
绝不！
- Ha ha! - Yeah!
哈哈！ - 是的！
Yeah, that's my girl!
是的，这才是我的女孩！
- Nice! - Yeah!
漂亮！ - 是的！
- What is it, honey? - What do you need, kiddo?
怎么了，亲爱的？ - 你需要什么，孩子？
Somebody call the wahmbulance.
有人叫救护车吗。
Duck,
鸭子，
duck,
goose.
鹅。
Hey! I got this.
嘿！我能搞定这个。
You're not the goose!
你不是那只鹅！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[Milbanks cheering]
[Milbanks欢呼]
That was so--so violent.
那真是——太暴力了。
Okay. Come on.
好吧。来吧。
Harper team meeting in the kitchen!
Harper团队在厨房开会！
We're gonna--
我们要——
it's okay, buddy.
没事的，伙计。
We're gonna whip these guys into--
我们要把这些家伙——
What is wrong with these people?
这些人怎么了？
You see it too?
你也看到了？
How could we not see it?
我们怎么可能没看到？
I thought they were gonna hurt you kids.
我以为他们会伤害你们这些孩子。
Thought?
以为？
Phil Jr.'s been punching me in the kidneys
菲尔小子的拳头一直往我肾脏上招呼
every chance he gets.
每次有机会就打。
[gasps] Me too!
我也是！
[all] Me too!
We had no idea they were gonna be like this.
我们完全没想到他们会这样。
I'm so sorry we invited them over.
很抱歉我们邀请了他们来。
Well...
嗯...
this might actually be kind of sort of maybe our fault.
这可能实际上有点儿，也许，是我们的错。
Your fault? How?
你的错？怎么会？
All you did was point out two customers
你只是指出两个需要在钓鱼区得到帮助的顾客。
that needed help in the fishing section.
[所有人] 嗯...
[all] Well...
我们可能安排你和他们认识
We might have set you up with them
这样你可以交朋友，我们就可以避开游戏之夜。
so you'd make friends and we could get out of game night.
但你喜欢游戏之夜。
But you love game night.
[所有人] 嗯...
[all] Well...
为什么你们不直接告诉我们？
Why didn't you just tell us?
你们为什么不直接告诉我们？
Because you guys love game night so much
因为你们太喜欢游戏之夜了
we didn't have the heart to tell you we hate it so much.
我们不忍心告诉你们我们其实很讨厌它。
Huh. Apparently you do have the heart.
呵，显然你们还是有这个心的。
Look, it's not that we hate spending time with you.
听着，并不是我们讨厌和你们共度时光。
It's just that sometimes
只是有时候
we'd rather hang out with our friends.
我们更愿意和朋友一起出去玩。
If we had just told you the truth,
如果我们当时就告诉你们真相，
we wouldn't be stuck with a family of kidney punchers
我们现在就不会被困在一群肾脏拳击手中间
in our living room.
在我们的客厅里。
[Phil] Harpers,
[Phil] 哈珀一家，
come out and pla-ay!
出来玩吧！
We are so sorry.
我们非常抱歉。
All right, listen.
好吧，听着。
I'm not gonna lie.
我不会撒谎。
We're a little disappointed.
我们有点失望。
That's a lie. We're a lot disappointed.
那是谎话。我们非常失望。
But right now, we have to deal with the Milbanks.
但现在，我们得应付米尔班克斯一家。
Let us do it.
让我们来处理吧。
We weren't honest with you,
我们没有对你们说实话，
so let us make up for it
所以让我们弥补这一点
by going out there and being honest with them.
通过出去那里并诚实地对待他们。
Hmm.
嗯。
- Wow. - That one takes after me.
- 哇。 - 那个像我。
[laughs]
[笑]
Mr. and Mrs. Milbank,
米尔班克先生和夫人，
we've been thinking about game night.
我们一直在考虑游戏之夜。
You know--
你知道--
Oh, whoa. Thinking time's over.
哦，哇。思考时间结束了。
We've had the mental challenges.
我们已经经历了心理挑战。
Now it gets physical.
现在要动真格了。
Now it gets physical?
现在要动真格了？
Yeah.
是的。
I want the old man.
我要那个老头。
Um, that is exactly what we were thinking.
嗯，这正是我们想的。
But first, you know, we're gonna go upstairs
但首先，你知道，我们要上楼
to get our boxing uniforms.
去拿我们的拳击服。
Yes! Our boxing uniforms.
对！我们的拳击服。
- Boxing uniforms! - Get ready to box!
- 拳击服！ - 准备好拳击！
Grr!
哼！
So, where are these boxing uniforms?
那么，这些拳击服在哪里？
There are no boxing uniforms, Dicky.
没有拳击服，Dicky。
Then what are we gonna wear when we box?
那我们打拳击时穿什么？
We're not gonna box!
我们不打拳击！
We're just gonna wait up here until they leave.
我们就在这里等到他们离开。
That's your plan?
这就是你的计划？
I'm a kid.
我还是个孩子。
We hide from stuff. It's what we do!
我们躲开事情。这是我们做的事！
You're right.
你说得对。
I'm the adult here. I should start acting like the adult.
我是成年人。我应该开始表现得像个成年人。
Listen, Phil.
听着，Phil。
I got to tell you something.
我得告诉你一件事。
Tomcat's tum-tum really hurts
Tomcat的肚子真的很痛
and he had to go to the hospital.
他不得不去医院。
- What are you doing? - I don't know!
- 你在干什么？ - 我不知道！
[stammering]
[结巴]
No, well, you didn't see us 'cause we left out the back door.
不，嗯，你没看到我们因为我们从后门出去了。
The upstairs back door.
楼上的后门。
Well, just let yourselves out
好吧，你们自己出去
and we'll see you all again real soon, okay?
我们很快会再见面的，好吗？
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
You got enough to worry about.
你们有足够的事情要担心了。
We'll just stay here and hold down the fort till you get back.
我们就在这里守着，直到你们回来。
No, no, no, you don't have to do that. We could be in the hospital all night.
不，不，不，你们不必这样做。我们可能在医院待一整晚。
Well, even more reason.
嗯，那就更有理由了。
Someone's got to stay here and feed the dog, right?
总得有人留在这里喂狗，对吧？
We left the dog down there.
我们把狗留在下面了。
Please do not stay at our house.
请不要留在我们家。
All right. Good.
好吧。很好。
They're not leaving.
他们不走。
Okay. New plan.
好的，新计划。
We call Josie and tell her to come house sit.
我们打电话给乔西，让她来照看房子。
Then the Milbanks will have to leave.
然后米尔班克一家就不得不离开了。
Mom, phone me.
妈妈，给我打电话。
[loud dance music]
[响亮的舞曲音乐]
♪ ♪
She's not picking up.
她没接电话。
We're just gonna have to wait them out up here
我们只能在这里等他们离开，
in this freezing cold attic.
在这冰冷的阁楼里。
Hey, I found some warmer clothes!
嘿，我找到了一些更暖和的衣服！
This is ridiculous.
这太荒唐了。
My family's up here shivering.
我的家人在这里冻得发抖。
What kind of a man am I?
我算什么男人？
There's only one thing to do:
只有一件事要做：
march down there and box a seven-year-old.
下去跟一个七岁小孩打一架。
Or,
或者，
we could climb out the window and camp out at the store.
我们可以从窗户爬出去，在商店里露营。
Now there's a kid with a plan.
现在有个孩子有计划了。
No, Tom, we are not putting our kids in jeopardy
不，汤姆，我们不能为了躲避一个一年级学生的殴打而让我们的孩子处于危险之中。
to avoid a beating from a first grader.
关上窗户！
Close the window!
[fluttering]
[扑腾声]
Shh.
嘘。
Do you hear that?
你听到那个声音了吗？
[all] Bat!
[所有人] 蝙蝠！
Open the window! Open the window!
打开窗户！打开窗户！
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
快！快！快！快！快！
[dull thud]
[沉闷的撞击声]
Shhh.
嘘。
What was that noise?
那是什么声音？
Sounds like intruders.
听起来像是入侵者。
Let's call the police.
我们报警吧。
- Yeah! - Battle stations. Let's go!
- 对！ - 准备战斗，走吧！
Come on, Milbanks.
快点，Milbanks。
Call police.
报警。
Guys, you can come out.
伙计们，你们可以出来了。
It must have flown out the window.
它一定是飞出窗外了。
- Are you guys okay? - Oh, that was so scary.
- 你们都没事吧？ - 哦，太吓人了。
You all right, tiger?
你还好吗，小虎？
Oh. Intense.
哦，真紧张。
Um...
嗯...
Dawn?
You have a little something.
你有点东西。
[bat shrieks]
[蝙蝠尖叫]
Can we please go out the window?
我们可以从窗户出去吗？
Yes!
是的！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
Any intruders come down here,
任何入侵者来到这里，
they're gonna get a Milspank!
他们都会得到一个Milspank！
Good one, Dad! Yeah!
干得好，爸爸！耶！
All right!
好的！
Nothing gets past the Milbanks!
没有什么能逃过米尔班克斯家的眼睛！
Let's go! Come on!
我们走！快点！
Follow me.
跟我来。
Police!
警察！
Hands on your heads.
双手放在头上。
Gosh.
天哪。
Officer, I can explain.
警官，我可以解释。
You can explain why you're breaking into this house?
你能解释为什么闯入这栋房子吗？
Oh, no, no, no, no, see.
哦，不，不，不，不，你看。
We weren't breaking in.
我们没有闯入。
We're breaking out.
我们是在逃出来。
We live here.
我们住在这里。
Okay. Let's see some I.D.
好吧。出示一下身份证。
Our wallets are in the house.
我们的钱包在屋里。
Then let's go in and you can get them.
那我们进去，你们可以拿。
We can't go in there.
我们不能进去。
It's a long story.
说来话长。
So you're telling me you'd rather be hauled down to the police station
所以你是说宁愿被带到警察局
than go back into your own house?
也不愿回到自己家里？
[all] Well...
好吧...
- Well done. - That was so good.
- 做得好。 - 真是太棒了。
You know, I got to admit, family game night did turn out to be pretty fun after all.
你知道吗，我得承认，家庭游戏之夜最终还是挺有趣的。
Yeah, glad we didn't miss this one.
是啊，很高兴我们没错过这次。
Whose turn is it?
轮到谁了？
- It's mine! - Okay!
- 轮到我了！ - 好的！
Your Harper family trivia category is:
你的哈珀家族知识问答类别是：
geography!
地理！
[all] Ooh!
哦！
Which great aunt moved to Santa Fe
哪位姑奶奶搬到了圣达菲
with her good friend, Esther?
和她好朋友埃丝特一起？
Your house guests confirmed your story.
你的客人证实了你的故事。
You're free to go home.
你可以回家了。
No, thanks.
不了，谢谢。
We're good.
我们没事。
Was it Aunt Wanda?
是旺达阿姨吗？
Yes, it was!
是的，就是她！
Woot, woot!
哇哦，哇哦！
- Woot, woot! - Woot, woot!
Nice wooting!
欢呼得好！
All right, who's next?
好的，下一位是谁？
[all shouting] - All right, all right, all right!
[众人齐声] - 好的，好的，好的！
Here we go: Which uncle did we bail out of this very cell?
我们从这个牢房里救出了哪位叔叔？
- ♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
- [发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是啊 ♪
- ♪
♪